RG 001:002, Records of the State of Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
Records of the State of Connecticut
1776-1933
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut
39 volumes
The official record books of the General Assembly.
RG001_002
T002509
Scope and Content
The official record books of the General Assembly.
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically in volumes numbered 1-39. These volumes are also numbered 12-45E within the larger collection of Early General Records (EGR).
Index Terms
Subjects:
Connecticut -- General Assembly -- Public records; Connecticut -- Politics and government -- Sources; Connecticut -- History -- Sources; Connecticut -- History -- Revolution, 1775-1783 -- Sources; Connecticut -- History -- War of 1812 -- Sources
Alternate Creator:
Connecticut. General Assembly
Restrictions on Access
Researchers should first consult use copies when available. See Alternate Form Available Section below.
See the policy.
Alternative Form Available
Volumes 1-23 microfilmed as part of. Volumes 1 is on Conn A.6 Reel 6; Volumes 2-3 are on Conn A.6 Reel 7; Volumes 4 is on Conn A.6 Reel 8; Volume 5 is on Conn A.6 Reel 9; Volumes 6 is on Conn A.6 Reel 10; Volume 7 is on Conn A.6 Reel 11; Volume 8 is on Conn A.6 Reel 12; Volume 9 is on Conn A.6 Reel 13; Volume 10 is on Conn A.6 Reel 14; Volume 11 is on Conn A.6 Reel 15; Volume 12 is on Conn A.6 Reel 16; Volumes 13-14 is on Conn A.6 Reel 17; Volumes 15-16 are on Conn A.6 Reel 18; Volumes 17-18 are on Conn A.6 Reel 19; Volumes 19-20 are on Conn A.6 Reel 20; Volumes 21-22 are on Conn A.6 Reel 21; Volume 23 is on Conn A.6 Reel 22.
Published as.
Inventory
- Records, 1776-1933
  See Restrictions on Access note above
  - 1776-1780 (Volume 1 / 12)
  - Index to State Records v. 1
  - 1780-1783 (Volume 2 / 13)
  - 1783-1787 (Volume 3 / 14)
  - 1787-1792 (Volume 4 / 15)
  - 1792-1797 (Volume 5 / 16)
  - 1797-1801 (Volume 6 / 17)
  - 1802-1805 (Volume 7 / 18)
  - 1805-1808 (Volume 8 / 19)
  - 1808-1811 (Volume 9 / 20)
  - 1812-1814 May (Volume 10 / 21)
  - 1814 October - 1816 May (Volume 11 / 22)
  - 1816-1818 (Volume 12 / 23)
  - 1819-1821 (Volume 13 / 24)
  - 1822-1823 (Volume 14 / 25)
  - 1824-1825 (Volume 15 / 26)
  - 1826-1827 (Volume 16 / 27)
  - 1828-1829 (Volume 17 / 28)
  - 1830-1831 (Volume 18 / 29)
  - 1832-1833 (Volume 19 / 30)
  - 1834-1835 (Volume 20 / 31)
  - 1836 (Volume 21 / 32)
  - 1837 (Volume 22 / 33)
  - 1838-1839 (Volume 23 / 34)
  - 1840-1841 (Volume 24 / 35)
  - 1842-1844 (Volume 25 / 36)
  - 1845-1847 (Volume 26 / 37)
  - 1848-1850 (Volume 27 / 38)
  - 1851-1853 (Volume 28 / 39)
  - 1854-1855 (Volume 29 / 40)
  - 1856-1858 (Volume 30 / 41)
  - 1859-1873 (Volume 31 / 42)
  - 1874-1886 (Volume 32 / 43)
  - 1887-1895 (Volume 33 / 44)
  - 1897-1905 (Volume 34 / 45)
  - 1907-1916 (Volume 35 / 45A)
  - 1917-1921 (Volume 36 / 45B)
  - 1921-1925 (Volume 37 / 45C)
  - 1927-1931 (Volume 38 / 45D)
  - 1931-1933 (Volume 39 / 45E)